U.S. Manpower Administration "Manpower Daily Reporter" Newsletters 5380
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- September, 1968; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday September 26, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday September 25, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday September 24, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday September 23, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday September 20, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday September 19, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday September 18, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday September 17, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday September 16, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday September 13, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday September 12, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday September 11, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday September 10, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday September 9, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday September 6, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday September 5, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday September 4, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday September 3, 1968. Item is in English.
- October, 1968; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday October 31, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday October 30, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday October 29, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday October 28, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Special Edition: Friday October 25, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday October 25, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday October 24, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday October 23, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday October 22, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday October 21, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday October 18, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday October 17, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday October 16, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday October 14, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday October 11, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday October 10, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday October 9, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday October 8, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday October 7, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday October 4, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday October 3, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday October 2, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday October 1, 1968. Item is in English.
- November, 1968; Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday November 29, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday November 27, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday November 26, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday November 25, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday November 22, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday November 21, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday November 20, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday November 19, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday November 18, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday November 15, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday November 14, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday November 13, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday November 12, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday November 8, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday November 7, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday November 6, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday November 5, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday November 4, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday November 1, 1968. Item is in English.
- December, 1968; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday December 30, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday December 27, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday December 26, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday December 24, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday December 23, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday December 19, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday December 18, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday December 13, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday December 12, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday December 10, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday December 6, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday December 5, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday December 4, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday December 3, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday December 2, 1968. Item is in English.
- January, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday January 31, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday January 30, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday January 29, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday January 28, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday January 27, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday January 24, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday January 23, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday January 22, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday January 21, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday January 17, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday January 16, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday January 15, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday January 14, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday January 13, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday January 10, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday January 9, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday January 8, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday January 7, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday January 6, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday January 2, 1969. Item is in English.
- February, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday February 27, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday February 26, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday February 25, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday February 19, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday February 12, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday February 10, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday February 7, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday February 6, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday February 5, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday February 4, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday February 3, 1969. Item is in English.
- March, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday March 28, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday March 27, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday March 26, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday March 25, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday March 24, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday March 20, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday March 17, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday March 14, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday March 12, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday March 11, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday March 10, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday March 4, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Copy 2. Tuesday March 4, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday March 3, 1969. Item is in English.
- April, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday April 30, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday April 29, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday April 25, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday April 24, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday April 23, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday April 22, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday April 21, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday April 18, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday April 17, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday April 16, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday April 15, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday April 11, 1969. Item is in English.